<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tm id="@SeatAreaNoObj$I">
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="eng"
  >This calibration involves powering the seat to the end stops of every supported axis.

For the calibration to be successful ensure the area surrounding the seat is free from any objects that will inhibit full movement.

Do not sit in the seat during the operation.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="nld"
  >Bij deze kalibrering moet u de stoel naar de eindaanslagen van elke ondersteunde richting verstellen.

Om de kalibrering met succes te kunnen uitvoeren, moet u eerst in de ruimte rondom de stoel controleren of er geen voorwerpen in de weg zitten, die de beweging kunnen blokkeren.

Tijdens deze bewerking mag u niet in de stoel zitten.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="fra"
  >Cet étalonnage nécessite le déplacement électrique du siège jusqu'aux butées d'extrémités sur tous les axes pris en charge.

Pour la réussite de l'étalonnage, vérifiez que la zone entourant le siège est exempte de tous objets pouvant faire obstacle au mouvement.

Ne vous asseyez pas sur le siège pendant l'opération.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="deu"
  >Bei dieser Kalibrierung wird der Sitz an die Endanschläge aller vorgesehenen Verstellachsen verfahren.

Damit die Kalibrierung erfolgreich verläuft, sicherstellen, dass der Bereich um den Sitz herum frei von Objekten ist, die eine vollständige Verstellung behindern könnten.

Während dieses Schrittes nicht auf dem Sitz sitzen.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="ita"
  >Questa taratura comporta l'azionamento del sedile fino ai fine corsa di ogni asse supportato.

Perché la taratura riesca, accertarsi che nell'area circostante al sedile non sia presente nessun oggetto che potrebbe impedire il completo movimento del sedile.

Non sedersi sul sedile durante l'operazione.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="jpn"
  >このキャリブレーションには、シートの全方向 (車両オプションにより異なる) エンドへの電動駆動が含まれます。

キャリブレーションを正しく完了するため、シートの動きを妨げる物がないよう、シート周辺エリアをクリアしなさい。

このオペレーション中、シートに腰掛けてはなりません。</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="ptg"
  >Esta calibragem envolve accionar o banco até aos batentes de todos os eixos suportados.

For the calibration to be successful ensure the area surrounding the seat is free from any objects that will inhibit full movement.
247     Para que a calibragem seja bem sucedida, certifique-se de que não existem quaisquer objectos que possam impedir o movimento total na zona à volta do banco.

Não se sente no banco durante a operação.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="ptb"
  >Essa calibração envolve o acionamento do assento até a parada final de cada eixo suportado.

Para que a calibragem seja bem-sucedida, verifique se a área ao redor do assento está livre de objetos que inibam o movimento total.

Não sente-se no assento durante a operação.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="rus"
  >Процедура калибровки заключается в перемещении сиденья до предельных положений по всем поддерживаемым осям.

Для успешного выполнения калибровки убедитесь, что вокруг сиденья отсутствуют какие-либо предметы, которые могут помешать перемещению.

Во время этой операции нельзя садиться на сиденье.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="esp"
  >Esta calibración implica la activación del asiento hasta los topes de cada eje que admite ajuste.

Para que la calibración sea satisfactoria, asegurarse de que la zona alrededor del asiento esté despejada de objetos que le limiten el movimiento.

No sentarse en el asiento durante la operación.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="chs"
  >此标定包括：使用动力装置将座椅移动至每个受支持的坐标轴的端部止动位置。

为成功标定，要确保座椅周围的区域没有任何会阻止完全运动的物体。

在操作过程中不要坐在座椅上。</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="kor"
  >이 보정에는 지원되는 모든 축의 엔드 스톱까지 시트에 전원을 공급하는 것이 포함되어 있습니다.

보정에 성공하려면 시트를 둘러싸고 있는 영역에 움직임을 방해하는 물체가 전혀 없는지 확인하십시오.

작동 중에는 시트에 앉지 마십시오.</tu>
</tm>
