<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tm id="@NGI_BLANK_RECOVERY_3_PHASE_3">
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="eng"
  >Once the application is complete select Configure existing module - Update to Phase 4: InControl Touch Pro application to complete the software update.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="nld"
  >Nadat de toepassing is uitgevoerd, selecteert u de toepassing Bestaande module configureren - Bijwerken naar Fase 4: InControl Touch Pro om de software-update uit te voeren.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="fra"
  >Une fois que l'application est terminée, sélectionnez Configurer le module existant - Mise à jour vers la phase 4 : application InControl Touch Pro pour terminer la mise à jour logicielle.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="deu"
  >Wenn die Anwendung abgeschlossen wurde, die folgende Anwendung auswählen, um die Softwareaktualisierung abzuschließen: „Vorhandenes Steuergerät konfigurieren“ – „Auf Phase 4 aktualisieren: InControl Touch Pro“.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="ita"
  >Al termine dell'applicazione, selezionare Configura modulo esistente - Aggiornamento a Fase 4: applicazione InControl Touch Pro per il completamento dell'aggiornamento software.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="jpn"
  >アプリケーションが完了したら、「既存モジュールの設定 - Phase 4 へのアップデート: InControl Touch Pro」アプリケーションを選択し、ソフトウェア アップデートを完了します。</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="ptg"
  >Após conclusão da aplicação, selecione a aplicação 'Configurar módulo existente - Atualizar para a fase 4: InControl Touch Pro' para concluir a atualização do software.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="ptb"
  >Assim que o aplicativo for concluído, selecione Configurar módulo existente - Atualize para Fase 4: InControl Touch Pro para concluir a atualização de software.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="rus"
  >После завершения работы приложения выберите приложение 'Программирование имеющегося блока — Обновление до версии Phase 4: InControl Touch Pro', чтобы завершить обновление программного обеспечения.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="esp"
  >Una vez que la aplicación se haya completado, seleccione Configurar módulo existente - Actualización a la fase 4: InControl Touch Pro para terminar la actualización de software.</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="chs"
  >应用程序完成后，选择“配置现有模块 - 更新到阶段 4：InControl 智能驭领 尊享触控”应用程序以完成软件更新。</tu>
	<tu
    xmlns:lang="kor"
  >응용 프로그램이 완료되는 대로 '기존 모듈 구성 - Phase 4로 업데이트: InControl Touch Pro' 응용 프로그램을 선택하여 소프트웨어 업데이트를 완료하십시오.</tu>
</tm>
